{
  "version": "1.0",
  "exportDate": "2026-12-18T00:00:00.000Z",
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Espa침ol A2",
      "icon": "游쀯릖",
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "calle",
          "back": "street"
        },
        {
          "front": "ciudad",
          "back": "city"
        },
        {
          "front": "pueblo",
          "back": "town"
        },
        {
          "front": "aldea",
          "back": "village"
        },
        {
          "front": "pa칤s",
          "back": "country"
        },
        {
          "front": "mundo",
          "back": "world"
        },
        {
          "front": "coche",
          "back": "car"
        },
        {
          "front": "autob칰s",
          "back": "bus"
        },
        {
          "front": "tren",
          "back": "train"
        },
        {
          "front": "avi칩n",
          "back": "plane"
        },
        {
          "front": "bicicleta",
          "back": "bicycle"
        },
        {
          "front": "taxi",
          "back": "taxi"
        },
        {
          "front": "estaci칩n",
          "back": "station"
        },
        {
          "front": "aeropuerto",
          "back": "airport"
        },
        {
          "front": "boleto",
          "back": "ticket"
        },
        {
          "front": "hotel",
          "back": "hotel"
        },
        {
          "front": "restaurante",
          "back": "restaurant"
        },
        {
          "front": "tienda",
          "back": "shop"
        },
        {
          "front": "tienda",
          "back": "store"
        },
        {
          "front": "mercado",
          "back": "market"
        },
        {
          "front": "banco",
          "back": "bank"
        },
        {
          "front": "oficina de correos",
          "back": "post office"
        },
        {
          "front": "hospital",
          "back": "hospital"
        },
        {
          "front": "escuela",
          "back": "school"
        },
        {
          "front": "universidad",
          "back": "university"
        },
        {
          "front": "biblioteca",
          "back": "library"
        },
        {
          "front": "museo",
          "back": "museum"
        },
        {
          "front": "cine",
          "back": "cinema"
        },
        {
          "front": "teatro",
          "back": "theater"
        },
        {
          "front": "parque",
          "back": "park"
        },
        {
          "front": "playa",
          "back": "beach"
        },
        {
          "front": "monta침a",
          "back": "mountain"
        },
        {
          "front": "r칤o",
          "back": "river"
        },
        {
          "front": "lago",
          "back": "lake"
        },
        {
          "front": "mar",
          "back": "sea"
        },
        {
          "front": "oc칠ano",
          "back": "ocean"
        },
        {
          "front": "bosque",
          "back": "forest"
        },
        {
          "front": "치rbol",
          "back": "tree"
        },
        {
          "front": "flor",
          "back": "flower"
        },
        {
          "front": "hierba",
          "back": "grass"
        },
        {
          "front": "cielo",
          "back": "sky"
        },
        {
          "front": "sol",
          "back": "sun"
        },
        {
          "front": "luna",
          "back": "moon"
        },
        {
          "front": "estrella",
          "back": "star"
        },
        {
          "front": "nube",
          "back": "cloud"
        },
        {
          "front": "lluvia",
          "back": "rain"
        },
        {
          "front": "nieve",
          "back": "snow"
        },
        {
          "front": "viento",
          "back": "wind"
        },
        {
          "front": "clima",
          "back": "weather"
        },
        {
          "front": "estaci칩n",
          "back": "season"
        },
        {
          "front": "primavera",
          "back": "spring"
        },
        {
          "front": "verano",
          "back": "summer"
        },
        {
          "front": "oto침o",
          "back": "autumn"
        },
        {
          "front": "invierno",
          "back": "winter"
        },
        {
          "front": "lunes",
          "back": "Monday"
        },
        {
          "front": "martes",
          "back": "Tuesday"
        },
        {
          "front": "mi칠rcoles",
          "back": "Wednesday"
        },
        {
          "front": "jueves",
          "back": "Thursday"
        },
        {
          "front": "viernes",
          "back": "Friday"
        },
        {
          "front": "s치bado",
          "back": "Saturday"
        },
        {
          "front": "domingo",
          "back": "Sunday"
        },
        {
          "front": "enero",
          "back": "January"
        },
        {
          "front": "febrero",
          "back": "February"
        },
        {
          "front": "marzo",
          "back": "March"
        },
        {
          "front": "abril",
          "back": "April"
        },
        {
          "front": "mayo",
          "back": "May"
        },
        {
          "front": "junio",
          "back": "June"
        },
        {
          "front": "julio",
          "back": "July"
        },
        {
          "front": "agosto",
          "back": "August"
        },
        {
          "front": "septiembre",
          "back": "September"
        },
        {
          "front": "octubre",
          "back": "October"
        },
        {
          "front": "noviembre",
          "back": "November"
        },
        {
          "front": "diciembre",
          "back": "December"
        },
        {
          "front": "hoy",
          "back": "today"
        },
        {
          "front": "ayer",
          "back": "yesterday"
        },
        {
          "front": "ma침ana",
          "back": "tomorrow"
        },
        {
          "front": "ma침ana",
          "back": "morning"
        },
        {
          "front": "tarde",
          "back": "afternoon"
        },
        {
          "front": "tarde/noche",
          "back": "evening"
        },
        {
          "front": "noche",
          "back": "night"
        },
        {
          "front": "d칤a",
          "back": "day"
        },
        {
          "front": "semana",
          "back": "week"
        },
        {
          "front": "mes",
          "back": "month"
        },
        {
          "front": "a침o",
          "back": "year"
        },
        {
          "front": "tiempo/hora",
          "back": "time"
        },
        {
          "front": "hora",
          "back": "hour"
        },
        {
          "front": "minuto",
          "back": "minute"
        },
        {
          "front": "segundo",
          "back": "second"
        },
        {
          "front": "temprano",
          "back": "early"
        },
        {
          "front": "tarde",
          "back": "late"
        },
        {
          "front": "ahora",
          "back": "now"
        },
        {
          "front": "pronto",
          "back": "soon"
        },
        {
          "front": "ya",
          "back": "already"
        },
        {
          "front": "todav칤a",
          "back": "still"
        },
        {
          "front": "siempre",
          "back": "always"
        },
        {
          "front": "nunca",
          "back": "never"
        },
        {
          "front": "a veces",
          "back": "sometimes"
        },
        {
          "front": "a menudo",
          "back": "often"
        },
        {
          "front": "usualmente",
          "back": "usually"
        },
        {
          "front": "trabajo",
          "back": "work"
        },
        {
          "front": "empleo",
          "back": "job"
        },
        {
          "front": "oficina",
          "back": "office"
        },
        {
          "front": "jefe",
          "back": "boss"
        },
        {
          "front": "trabajador",
          "back": "worker"
        },
        {
          "front": "empleado",
          "back": "employee"
        },
        {
          "front": "profesor",
          "back": "teacher"
        },
        {
          "front": "estudiante",
          "back": "student"
        },
        {
          "front": "m칠dico",
          "back": "doctor"
        },
        {
          "front": "enfermera",
          "back": "nurse"
        },
        {
          "front": "conductor",
          "back": "driver"
        },
        {
          "front": "cocinero",
          "back": "cook"
        },
        {
          "front": "camarero",
          "back": "waiter"
        },
        {
          "front": "polic칤a",
          "back": "police"
        },
        {
          "front": "abogado",
          "back": "lawyer"
        },
        {
          "front": "ingeniero",
          "back": "engineer"
        },
        {
          "front": "artista",
          "back": "artist"
        },
        {
          "front": "cantante",
          "back": "singer"
        },
        {
          "front": "actor",
          "back": "actor"
        },
        {
          "front": "escritor",
          "back": "writer"
        },
        {
          "front": "dinero",
          "back": "money"
        },
        {
          "front": "precio",
          "back": "price"
        },
        {
          "front": "costo",
          "back": "cost"
        },
        {
          "front": "barato",
          "back": "cheap"
        },
        {
          "front": "caro",
          "back": "expensive"
        },
        {
          "front": "gratis",
          "back": "free"
        },
        {
          "front": "rico",
          "back": "rich"
        },
        {
          "front": "pobre",
          "back": "poor"
        },
        {
          "front": "color",
          "back": "color"
        },
        {
          "front": "blanco",
          "back": "white"
        },
        {
          "front": "negro",
          "back": "black"
        },
        {
          "front": "rojo",
          "back": "red"
        },
        {
          "front": "azul",
          "back": "blue"
        },
        {
          "front": "verde",
          "back": "green"
        },
        {
          "front": "amarillo",
          "back": "yellow"
        },
        {
          "front": "naranja",
          "back": "orange"
        },
        {
          "front": "marr칩n",
          "back": "brown"
        },
        {
          "front": "gris",
          "back": "grey"
        },
        {
          "front": "rosa",
          "back": "pink"
        },
        {
          "front": "morado",
          "back": "purple"
        },
        {
          "front": "ropa",
          "back": "clothes"
        },
        {
          "front": "camisa",
          "back": "shirt"
        },
        {
          "front": "pantalones",
          "back": "pants"
        },
        {
          "front": "vestido",
          "back": "dress"
        },
        {
          "front": "falda",
          "back": "skirt"
        },
        {
          "front": "abrigo",
          "back": "coat"
        },
        {
          "front": "chaqueta",
          "back": "jacket"
        },
        {
          "front": "zapatos",
          "back": "shoes"
        },
        {
          "front": "calcetines",
          "back": "socks"
        },
        {
          "front": "sombrero",
          "back": "hat"
        },
        {
          "front": "gafas",
          "back": "glasses"
        },
        {
          "front": "reloj",
          "back": "watch"
        },
        {
          "front": "anillo",
          "back": "ring"
        },
        {
          "front": "cuerpo",
          "back": "body"
        },
        {
          "front": "cabeza",
          "back": "head"
        },
        {
          "front": "cara",
          "back": "face"
        },
        {
          "front": "ojo",
          "back": "eye"
        },
        {
          "front": "oreja",
          "back": "ear"
        },
        {
          "front": "nariz",
          "back": "nose"
        },
        {
          "front": "boca",
          "back": "mouth"
        },
        {
          "front": "diente",
          "back": "tooth"
        },
        {
          "front": "lengua",
          "back": "tongue"
        },
        {
          "front": "labio",
          "back": "lip"
        },
        {
          "front": "cabello",
          "back": "hair"
        },
        {
          "front": "cuello",
          "back": "neck"
        },
        {
          "front": "hombro",
          "back": "shoulder"
        },
        {
          "front": "brazo",
          "back": "arm"
        },
        {
          "front": "mano",
          "back": "hand"
        },
        {
          "front": "dedo",
          "back": "finger"
        },
        {
          "front": "pierna",
          "back": "leg"
        },
        {
          "front": "pie",
          "back": "foot"
        },
        {
          "front": "rodilla",
          "back": "knee"
        },
        {
          "front": "espalda",
          "back": "back"
        },
        {
          "front": "pecho",
          "back": "chest"
        },
        {
          "front": "est칩mago",
          "back": "stomach"
        },
        {
          "front": "coraz칩n",
          "back": "heart"
        },
        {
          "front": "sangre",
          "back": "blood"
        },
        {
          "front": "animal",
          "back": "animal"
        },
        {
          "front": "perro",
          "back": "dog"
        },
        {
          "front": "gato",
          "back": "cat"
        },
        {
          "front": "p치jaro",
          "back": "bird"
        },
        {
          "front": "caballo",
          "back": "horse"
        },
        {
          "front": "vaca",
          "back": "cow"
        },
        {
          "front": "cerdo",
          "back": "pig"
        },
        {
          "front": "pollo",
          "back": "chicken"
        },
        {
          "front": "rat칩n",
          "back": "mouse"
        },
        {
          "front": "le칩n",
          "back": "lion"
        },
        {
          "front": "elefante",
          "back": "elephant"
        },
        {
          "front": "oso",
          "back": "bear"
        },
        {
          "front": "tigre",
          "back": "tiger"
        },
        {
          "front": "mono",
          "back": "monkey"
        },
        {
          "front": "tel칠fono",
          "back": "phone"
        },
        {
          "front": "computadora",
          "back": "computer"
        },
        {
          "front": "televisi칩n",
          "back": "television"
        },
        {
          "front": "radio",
          "back": "radio"
        },
        {
          "front": "c치mara",
          "back": "camera"
        },
        {
          "front": "imagen",
          "back": "picture"
        },
        {
          "front": "foto",
          "back": "photo"
        },
        {
          "front": "m칰sica",
          "back": "music"
        },
        {
          "front": "canci칩n",
          "back": "song"
        },
        {
          "front": "pel칤cula",
          "back": "film"
        },
        {
          "front": "juego",
          "back": "game"
        },
        {
          "front": "deporte",
          "back": "sport"
        },
        {
          "front": "f칰tbol",
          "back": "football"
        },
        {
          "front": "tenis",
          "back": "tennis"
        },
        {
          "front": "nataci칩n",
          "back": "swimming"
        },
        {
          "front": "pelota",
          "back": "ball"
        },
        {
          "front": "equipo",
          "back": "team"
        },
        {
          "front": "ganar",
          "back": "win"
        },
        {
          "front": "perder",
          "back": "lose"
        },
        {
          "front": "carta",
          "back": "letter"
        },
        {
          "front": "correo electr칩nico",
          "back": "email"
        },
        {
          "front": "mensaje",
          "back": "message"
        },
        {
          "front": "noticias",
          "back": "news"
        },
        {
          "front": "historia",
          "back": "story"
        },
        {
          "front": "palabra",
          "back": "word"
        },
        {
          "front": "idioma",
          "back": "language"
        },
        {
          "front": "pregunta",
          "back": "question"
        },
        {
          "front": "respuesta",
          "back": "answer"
        },
        {
          "front": "idea",
          "back": "idea"
        },
        {
          "front": "problema",
          "back": "problem"
        },
        {
          "front": "soluci칩n",
          "back": "solution"
        },
        {
          "front": "error",
          "back": "mistake"
        },
        {
          "front": "edad",
          "back": "age"
        },
        {
          "front": "cumplea침os",
          "back": "birthday"
        },
        {
          "front": "fiesta",
          "back": "party"
        },
        {
          "front": "regalo",
          "back": "gift"
        },
        {
          "front": "vacaciones",
          "back": "holiday"
        },
        {
          "front": "Navidad",
          "back": "Christmas"
        },
        {
          "front": "cena",
          "back": "dinner"
        },
        {
          "front": "almuerzo",
          "back": "lunch"
        },
        {
          "front": "desayuno",
          "back": "breakfast"
        },
        {
          "front": "comida",
          "back": "meal"
        },
        {
          "front": "sabor",
          "back": "taste"
        },
        {
          "front": "olor",
          "back": "smell"
        },
        {
          "front": "dulce",
          "back": "sweet"
        },
        {
          "front": "agrio",
          "back": "sour"
        },
        {
          "front": "amargo",
          "back": "bitter"
        },
        {
          "front": "picante",
          "back": "spicy"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}